

JUAN DE SANTOS

JR. FRONT-END DEVELOPER

+49 0178 5546224

juanj.desantos@gmail.com

LinkedIn: Juan de Santos

Berlin, Germany

HELLO, I'm Jr. Front-End Developer from Spain, currently residing in Germany since 2018, with a background in others work fields. In 2022, I made the decision to embrace new challenges and explore the world of programming. The learning process, which initially presented difficulties, unexpectedly revealed a source of joy and satisfaction. I've gained previous experience in developing my own projects and am looking for the opportunity to work as a professional programmer.

SKILLS

Hard-working

Look for solutions

Dedicated

Enthusiastic

Methodical

Trustworthy

Team Player

KNOWLEDGE



HTML



CSS



Javascript



React



API



Github



Scrum

LANGUAGES

English B1 • • • 0 0 0

WORK EXPERIENCE

> RETTUNGSSANITÄTER

Gorris Krankentransport GmbH. Berlin, Germany. *Apr 2018 - May 2023*

Responsible for transporting patients from point A to point B while also providing emotional support and empathy. In addition, management of Human Resources tasks, including recruiting new colleagues in Spain, as well as managing and translating during job interviews.

> TECHNICIAN AND EVENT ASSISTANT

Track 13 S.L. Segovia, Spain.

Jun 2016 - Mar 2018

Management of motor vehicles and transport of materials to events providing audiovisual services across Spain. During these events, I also provided technical assistance.

> DATA PROTECTION CONSULTANT

Segoval S.L. Segovia, Spain.

Feb 2016 - Jun 2016

Assisting companies with implementing Constitutional Law related to data protection. My responsibilities included acquiring new clients and providing technical advice on-site.

> PRODUCTION TECHNICIAN FOR EVENTS AND SHOWS

Dos Eventos S.L. Segovia, Spain.

Oct 2008 - Nov 2015

Transportation, organization and assembly management for events of any size.

EDUCATION

> FRONT END DEVELOPER

Developer Akademie. Münich, Germany. 2023

> SPECIALIST IN EMERGENCY HEALT CARE

I.E.S. Ezequiel González, Health. Segovia, Spain.

2017